Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Collection, Part II: Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- Series II: Non-digitized Tapes, 1956-2001
  - II:A Private Recordings
    - Green Fields of America (group) Rehearal in San Juan, Puerto Rico. Musicians include: Liz Carroll (fiddle), Jack Coen (flute), Fr. Charlie Coen (concertina), Mick Moloney (guitar), Sean McGlynn (accordion), Bill Ochs (uillieann pipes). (Length: 01:30:00), May 2, 1979 (Box 14, Item aiamm381R)
    - Green Fields of America (group) Rehearsal for a show at International House, Philadelphia, PA. Musicians: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Liz Carroll (fiddle), Mick Moloney (banjo, guitar), Jack Coen (flute), Charlie Coen (concertina), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar). (Length: 00:25:00), Oct 1, 1984 (Box 25, Item aiamm651C)
    - Green Fields of America (group) Labeled "Rehearsal for Record." Musicians include: Jimmy Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Eileen Ivers (fiddle). Moloney narrates arrangements. (Length: 00:45:00), Jun, 1988 (Box 25, Item aiamm652C)
    - Green Grass Cloggers (group) Susie Goff and other old time players play tunes for Moloney in preparation for the Festival of Mountaint Music and Dance. (Length: 00:45:00), circa 1985 (Box 25, Item aiamm653C)
    - Green Grass Cloggers (group) Interview. Members of the North Carolina dance troupe discuss their origins and organization. (Length: 00:25:00), Dec 4, 1986 (Box 25, Item aiamm654C)
    - Harbison, Janet (harp) Interview. Harbison discusses her life and music. (Length: 00:45:00), Nov 4, 1992 (Box 25, Item aiamm655C)
    - Harte, Frank (vocals) Labeled "Chapelizod." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Jun 9, 1975 (Box 27, Item aiamm656C)
    - Harte, Frank (vocals) Private performance of "King Williamstown" recorded over the phone. (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm657C)
    - Hay Down Treaders (group) Demo tape featuring Tim Britton (uilleann pipes, whistle) and Mark Simos (fiddle, guitar, vocals). (Length: 00:15:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm658C)
    - Hayes, Martin (fiddle) Audio letter to Jimmy Keane featuring private recordings of twenty-year old Hayes including the latter's compositions (15 minutes) followed by private performances by Jimmy Keane (accordion) (20 minutes). (Total length: 00:35:00), post 1982 (Box 25, Item aiamm659C)
    - Henry, Dermot (guitar, singer, entertainer) Interview on cruise ship. Henry discusses his life, music, showbands and performing in the U.S. (Length: 00:30:00), Jan 17, 1992 (Box 25, Item aiamm660C)
    - Irish Tradition: Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals) Practice session of tunes and songs in Washington, D.C. (Length: 00:40:00), Jul, 1987 (Box 25, Item aiamm661C)
    - Irish Tradition: Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O'Brien (guitar) Labeled "Rough Mix." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm382R)
    - Ivers, Eileen (fiddle) Interview about life, music and competing featuring some unaccompanied private performances by thirteen-year old Ivers (10 minutes; Dec 6, 1978); Mulvihill, Gail (banjo, fiddle), Mulvihill, Martin (fiddle) Interview with thirteen-year old Gail and private unaccompanied performance by Martin (10 minutes; Jan 9, 1978); Britton, Tim (uilleann pipes) Ruth, Ben (fiddle) Interview with Britton and private performance (25 minutes); Posen, Shelley (guitar), Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Recording session of "O'Neill's Hornpipe" (5 minutes; Jan 4, 1979). (Total length: 00:50:00), Dec 6, 1978, Jan 4, 1979, and Jan 9, 1979 (Box 25, Item aiamm662C)
    - Ivers, Eileen (fiddle) Studio rough mixes for the album, Hold the Line. (Length: 00:50:00), 1994 (Box 25, Item aiamm663C)
    - Jacobs, Ellen (fiddle) Private performance and interview in Philadelphia, PA. with the Ann Arbor transplant about her involvement with Irish music. (Length: 00:20:00), Dec 29, 1977 (Box 25, Item aiamm664C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Interview in New Canaan, CT. upon completion of a recording for Green Linnet. Keane discusses his life and music. (Length: 00:40:00), Aug 8, 1979 (Box 25, Item aiamm665C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Labeled "Interview." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], Aug 9, 1979 (Box 17, Item aiamm384R)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Unaccompanied accordion rough mixes for the 1980 LP Roll Away the Reel World. (Length: 00:30:00), Aug, 1979 (Box 25, Item aiamm666C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Interview by Leslie Austin promoting the album Roll Away the Reel World with music excerpts. (Length: 00:30:00), 1982 (Box 25, Item aiamm668C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Performances and interview for the radio program, "Roll Away the Reel World" produced by Leslie Austin. Master copy. (Length: 00:30:00), 1982 (Box 14, Item aiamm385R)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Private performnace of tunes. (Length: 00:30:00), Oct 7, 1987 (Box 25, Item aiamm669C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Labeled "Record Practice." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm672C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) Studio recording session with engineer announcing takes. (Length: 00:15:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm670C)
    - Keane, James (accordion) [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm673C)
    - Keane, James (accordion), Keane, Paddy. Labeled "Recorded From James Keane's Tape." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm674C)
    - Keane, James (accordion), McGlynn, Sean (accordion), Connolly, Mattie (uilleann pipes), Conway, Brian (fiddle) Labeled "Practice, NY." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm675C)
    - Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (banjo) Recording session at Keane's apartment in Queens (10 minutes); Fitzpatrick, John (accordion), Fitzpatrick, Maureen (fiddle) Recording session in Long Island. (25 minutes) (Total length:00:35:00), Jan 22, 1977 (Box 14, Item aiamm383R)
    - Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar) and unidentified fiddle. Recording session for Roll Away the Reel World with engineer calling takes. (Length:01:00:00), circa 1980 (Box 25, Item aiamm667C)
    - Keane, James (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar) Rough overmodulated studio mixes with count-offs and engineer for the album, Roll Away the Reel World. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm671C)
    - Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Phone interview about composing tunes (5 minutes); commercial recording of "Barefoot in Gettysburg" played over the phone; all of this is taped over Moloney overdubbing onto rough studio mixes of unidentified record. (Total length: 00:30:00), Apr 26. 1985 (Box 25, Item aiamm676C)
    - Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Labeled "Tunes 86." Keane introduces and performs tunes for Moloney and Robbie O'Connell. (Length: 00:25:00), 1986 (Box 25, Item aiamm677C)
    - Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Labeled "West Coast 93-New Tunes/Order." Compilation tape on which Keane outlines a concert set list for Moloney by alternating private performances and commercial recordings. (Length: 01:00:00), 1993 (Box 25, Item aiamm678C)
    - Keane, Tommy (uilleann pipes, flute, banjo) Homemade high-quality private performances. (Length: 00:15:00), Jul 1, 1979 (Box 25, Item aiamm679C)
    - Keegan, Kevin (accordion) Performances in multiple field recording situations. (Length: 01:30:00), pre 1978 (Box 25, Item aiamm680C)
    - Keenan, Paddy (low whistle) Private performance of tunes and airs. Poor sound quality. (Length:00:10:00), Mar 1, 1980 (Box 25, Item aiamm681C)
    - Kelly, Gene (accordion), Teahan, Terry "Cuz" (melodeon) Master mixes for the 1977 Topic LP, Old Time Irish Music in America. (Length: 00:30:00) (Box 14, Item aiamm386R)
    - Kelly, Gene (accordion), Teahan, Terry "Cuz" (melodeon) Master mixes for the 1977 Topic LP, Old Time Irish Music in America. (Length: 00:30:00) (Box 14, Item aiamm387R)
    - Kelly, Gene (accordion), Collins, Gus (flute) Recording session in the Bronx. (Length: 00:40:00), Oct 2 (Box 14, Item aiamm388R)
    - Kelly, Gene (accordion), Mahon, James (piano) [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm682C)
    - Kelly, Gene (accordion), Teahan, Terry (accordion) [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm683C)
    - Kelly, James (fiddle), O'Brien, Paddy (accordion), Sproule, Daithi (guitar, vocals) Audio letter from Kelly to Moloney. Kelly introduces private performances by the trio. (Length: 00:30:00), late 1970s (Box 25, Item aiamm684C)
    - Kelly, James (fiddle), O'Brien, Paddy (accordion), Sproule, Daithi (guitar, vocals) [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm685C)
    - Kelly, Jimmy. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm687C)
    - Kelly, Jimmy (vocals, guitar) and "Donna and Pat." Labeled "Irish American Songs, Practice Tape For Nash. Concert." Two vaudeville medleys with close harmony, guitar and Rhodes. (Length:00:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm686C)
    - Kelly, Micky (vocals, stories) Private performances from Draperstown, Derry singer storyteller recorded and introduced by Bill Ochs as a demo. (Length:00:30:00, 1978 (Box 25, Item aiamm688C)
    - Knock na Shee (group) Demo featuring Jo Allen, Marty Somberg and Mark Simos. (Length: 00:30:00), undated (Box 14, Item aiamm389R)
    - Lilly, John (mandolin) Audio letter to Moloney from West Virginian Lilly playing and teaching standard old time repertoire. (Length: 01:00:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm689C)
    - MacMaster, Natalie (fiddle) Private performances from the fifteen-year old Cape Bretoner. (Length: 00:20:00), 1980s (Box 25, Item aiamm690C)
    - MacMathuna, Ciaran (broadcaster, b. Nov 26, 1925, Limerick, d. Dec 11, 2009) Interview in Dublin. Broadcaster MacMathuna discusses traditional music on Irish radio and television and his own broadcasting career in Ireland and the U.S.(Length: 00:30:00), Apr 3, 1980 (Box 14, Item aiamm390R)
    - MacMathuna, Seamus (singer) Audio letter to Moloney. MacMathuna and wife introduce private performances of songs and a field recording of a song recorded in Miltown Malbay (15 minutes); tunes performed and introduced by Eddie Moloney from Ballinakill, Co Galway (15 minutes); rough mixes of unidentified fiddle, flute and guitar. (Total length: 01:00:00), mid 1980s (Box 25, Item aiamm691C)
    - MacNamara, Josephine (dancer) Solo whistle medley for MacNamara's tap routine recorded on low-fi tape recorder. (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm692C)
    - Maguire, Manus (fiddle), Maguire, Seamus (fiddle) Private performance of unaccompanied fiddles. (Length: 01:00:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm693C)
    - Makem, Tommy (vocals, whistle) Interview in San Francisco, CA. The entertainer discusses his life and career. (Length: 01:30:00), Oct 11, 1991 (Box 25, Item aiamm694C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion) Private performances of tunes with spoken introductions (40 minutes); Irish Tradition: Billy McComiskey (accordion), Brendan Mulvihill (fiddle), Andy O'Brien (guitar, vocals) Pub concert performance (45 minutes). (Total length: 01:25:00), Jul 23, 1979 (Box 25, Item aiamm695C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion) Rough mixes for the album, Makin' the Rounds. (Length: 00:45:00), Mar 1, 1981 (Box 25, Item aiamm696C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion) [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Mar 25, 1981 (Box 27, Item aiamm697C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion) Recording session with engineer count-offs featuring fiddle and guitar. (Length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm700C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion) Rough mixes, unaccompanied and with guitar and fiddle. (Length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm699C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion), Egan, Seamus (mandolin) Private performances for Moloney with spoken tune identifications. (Length: 00:20:00), Mar 7, 1985 (Box 25, Item aiamm698C)
    - McComiskey, Billy (accordion), Mulvihill, Brendan (fiddle) Recording session labeled "Tape 7." (Length:01:00:00), undated (Box 14, Item aiamm391R)
    - McCullough, L. E. (whistle) Recording session of "Love at the Endings" unaccompanied and with guitar. (Length: 00:15:00), Nov 14, 1971 (Box 14, Item aiamm392R)
    - McCullough, L. E. (whistle), Edelman, Larry (guitar) Recording session in Pittsburgh, PA. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Feb 18, 1978 (Box 17, Item aiamm393R)
    - McDonagh, Larry, McDonagh, Michael. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm701C)
    - McDonagh, Mary (organizer) Interview with secretary of the Irish Musicians' Association of Chicago branch of Comhaltas and Midwest Coordinator for Comhaltas, at Terry "Cuz" Teahan's house as part of the Chicago Ethnic Arts Project. McDonagh discusses Comhaltas, the Fleadh, traditional music in Chicago, step dancing (35 minutes); interview with Terry Teahan about needlepainting, embroidery and instruments. (25 minutes) (Total length: 01:00:00) Original tapes are at the American Folklife Center., May 5, 1977 (Box 14, Item aiamm394R)
    - McEchran, Mary and John and Lou O'Grady. Labeled "Interview." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm702C)
    - McGann, Andy (fiddle, b. New York, Oct 5, 1928, d. New York, Jul 14, 2004), Shannon, Joe (uilleann pipes), McGreevy, Johhny (fiddle) Compilation of interview excerpts separated with leader for the radio series, Across the Western Ocean. (Length: 01:00:00), post 1977 (Box 14, Item aiamm395R)
    - McGlynn, Sean (accordion), Moloney, Mick (guitar) Recording session at Sean McGlynn's home. (Length: 00:20:00), Jan 20, 1976 (Box 14, Item aiamm396R)
    - McGlynn, Sean (accordion), Flynn, Mike (flute), Moloney, Mick (guitar) Recording session at McGlynn's home in Long Island. (Length: 00:45:00), Jan 22, 1977 (Box 14, Item aiamm397R)
    - McGovern, Betsy (vocals, guitar) Demo of "Beth's Lullaby" by New Orleans based singer songwriter. (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm703C)
    - McGovern, Betsy (vocals, guitar) Labeled "Betsy and Patrick for Mick II." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm705C)
    - McGovern, Betsy (vocals, guitar) Three rough studio mixes from the New Orleans singer songwriter. (Length: 00:15:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm704C)
    - McGreevy, Johhny (fiddle), Shannon, Joe (uilleann pipes), McCullough, L.E. (whistle), Cooley, Seamus (flute), Cooley, Mary (vocals). [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Mar 24, 1976-Mar 25, 1976 (Box 27, Item aiamm706C)
    - McGreevy, Johnny (fiddle), Shannon, Joe (uilleann pipes) [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm398R)
    - McKenna, Joe (uilleann pipes), Mick Moloney, Fr. Charlie Coen, Charlie Campbell and Eddie Cahill (flute). [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], Oct 3, 1977 (Box 17, Item aiamm399R)
    - McKenna, Joe (uilleann pipes) [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm708C)
    - McKenna, Joe (uilleann pipes), Moloney, Mick (mandolin, guitar) Labeled "Tape for Record." Private McKenna performance over the phone followed by Moloney practicing. (Length: 00:10:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm707C)
    - McKenzie, Laura (flute), Bronson, Patty (guitar). 8 track master including "Jigs," and "Reels.", undated (Box 21, Item aiamm400R)
    - McLain, Steve (flute) Demo duets with Mike McKinley and Jeremiah McLane. (Length: 00:30:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm709C)
    - McNulty, Eileen (entertainer, b. 1915, N. Attleboro, MA) Part one of interview in North Bergen, NJ. A member of the McNulty Family, Eileen discusses her personal and musical history. (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 2, 1982 (Box 14, Item aiamm401R)
    - McNulty, Eileen (entertainer, b. 1915, N. Attleboro, MA) Part two of interview in North Bergen, NJ. A member of the McNulty Family, Eileen discusses her personal and musical history. (Length: 01:00:00), Oct 2, 1982 (Box 14, Item aiamm402R)
    - Milner, Dan (vocals) Labeled "Dan Milner's Greatest Hits Vol. I." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm711C)
    - Milner, Dan (vocals) Labeled "#2." Private performances of unaccompanied songs including log with titles and keys. (Length: 00:40:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm710C)
    - Milner, Dan (vocals), Cole, Larry (Northumberland pipes), Kaplan, Paul (guitar) Private performance or demo. (Length 01:00:00), undated (Box 21, Item aiamm403R)
    - Mogan-Mattison, Sue (vocals) Demo. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm712C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals) Labeled "Ulster Songs. Original tape sent to Mags." Audio letter from Moloney while residing with Kenny Goldstein in Philadelphia, PA. He discusses beginning his studies (10 minutes) then plays snippets of the commercial recording, Songs of Irish Civil Rights for Mags to transcribe for a proposed book for Oak publications.(40 minutes). (Total length: 00:50:00), pre 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm713C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, mandolin, vocals) Private performances of tunes and songs; sounds like a demo. (Length: 01:00:00), 1974 (Box 25, Item aiamm714C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Labeled "Own Record 1984 Jigs Final Mix." Studio mix of jig set with mandolin, whistle, accordion and flute for the album, Uncommon Bonds. (Length:00:10:00) (Box 25, Item aiamm715C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Labeled "Tunes to Learn." Moloney practices tunes. (Length: 00:15:00), 1984 (Box 25, Item aiamm716C)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo) Labeled "Miltown Malbay 1985." Moloney records tunes on banjo to learn/remember, taped over various Miltown sessions at Friel’s, Conway’s, Clancy’s pubs; excerpts from Willie Clancy Week concert including Moloney performance with Jimmy Keane and Robbie O'Connell; commercial recordings played back in a room: trad w/harpsichord, female singer, Gavin and Lennon; more concert. (Total length: 01:00:00) (Box 25, Item aiamm718C)
    - Moloney, Mick (dictation) South American Tour Report. Moloney dictates journal of the Festival of Mountain Music and Dance tour. (Length: 00:40:00), c. 1985 (Box 26, Item aiamm1230C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, banjo, vocals) 16-track Morning Star Studios master featuring "O’Hara, Hughes, McReesh and Sands," "Bonnie Blue-Eyed Nancy.", Oct 30 (Box 21, Item aiamm406R)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo) Labeled "Out of Ireland #2." Rough mixes for the documentary film, Out of Ireland. Musicians include: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jimmy Keane (accordion). (Length:00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm722C)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo) Rehearsal for the soundtrack to the documentary film, Out of Ireland. Musicians include: Jerry O'Sullivan (uilleann pipes), Eileen Ivers (fiddle), Seamus Egan (flute, banjo), Jimmy Keane (accordion). (Length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm723C)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo) Rough mixes for the 1995 PBS documentary film, Out of Ireland. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm724C)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo) Rough mixes for the 1995 PBS documentary film, Out of Ireland. (Length: 01:00:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm725C)
    - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo) Labeled "James, Robbie and Self Practice and Timmy Britton." [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 27, Item aiamm732C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Labeled "Tunes for Record, Tunes to Learn." Side A: Compilation of commercial recordings. Side B: Private performances of tunes by mandolin and unidentified accordion and some four-track mandolin experiments. (Length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm726C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Labeled "Tunes for Record." Moloney plays mandolin for reference (20 minutes) followed by one rough studio mix of "We Built Sandcastles, McKeown and I." (Total length: 00:25:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm727C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Mixed reference tape for Moloney's personal use labeled "Own Tunes and Frank Harte." Informal recording session with Frank Harte (vocals); Billy McComiskey plays tunes; Moloney plays tunes on mandolin; recording of a 78; Harte gives lyrics over the phone. (Total length: 00:45:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm728C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin) Overdubbed four-part mandolin arrangement of "Bill Harte's Jig." (Length: 00:05:00), undated (Box 25, Item aiamm729C)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin, vocals) Moloney practices songs and tunes with mandolin accompaniment (10 minutes) preceded by doo wop acappella group singing three songs including "Danny Boy." (Total length: 00:20:00), undated (Box 14, Item aiamm410R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) 8-track Morning Star Studios master tape with harp and pipes labeled "An Old Irish Song" and "Reels.", undated (Box 22, Item aiamm416R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) 8-track Morning Star Studios master tape with track sheets labeled "Reel #2" including "Mussorka," "Miss Fogarty's Cake," "Muldoon Solid Man," "St. Brendan's Fair Isle.", undated (Box 22, Item aiamm417R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) Labeled "2 Whistles Edited." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 24, Item aiamm414R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) Labeled "Album #1 Mixes." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 24, Item aiamm415R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) Labeled "Banjo / Mandolin Record." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm412R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) Labeled "Banjo / Mandolin Record." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm411R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo) Labeled "Copy of Master SIF 1027 Banjo / Mandolin Record." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm413R)
    - Moloney, Mick. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm408R)
    - Moloney, Mick. [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 15, Item aiamm409R)
    - Moloney, Mick. [Needs some preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 17, Item aiamm407R)
    - Moloney, Mick (mandolin), Fahey, Marty (piano) Recording session. (Length: 00:30:00), May 4 (Box 14, Item aiamm405R)
    - Moloney, Mick (banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (guitar) Labeled "Tape for Jimmy; Tunes 1993 Tour." Rehearsal tape (Length: 00:45:00) (Box 26, Item aiamm1235C)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Studio mixes for the album, There Were Roses. (Length: 00:20:00), circa 1993 (Box 14, Item aiamm404R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Labeled "Master for There Were Roses - Side II." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 22, Item aiamm419R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Master for side one of the album, There Were Roses., undated (Box 22, Item aiamm420R)
    - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), Keane, Jimmy (accordion), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar) Morning Star Studio tape with log labeled "#3: Stick to the Crathur, Every Circum, Hornpipes etc." [Needs significant preservation work before digitization.], undated (Box 24, Item aiamm418R)